Oh mom brother, I heard someone's voice, which
animal's voice was this,
brother, it must have been someone's, I don't know, let's go
out and see,
brother, no brother, the
voice was coming from this place, look from somewhere, I can see
some shadow, it will come
behind, shout, I mean,
hey here, we will not be able to stay here at night, friend,
come on, come on, I left you, go behind, go ahead, go ahead, come on, come on,
friends,
after coming in the car, we got some peace,
friends, this area that you guys are seeing is the
area behind our house and this is a
forest and in this forest live some wild
animals like fox, wild dog, wild
boar and yes, those also live who
eat the flesh of dead animals and dead humans.
So let me tell you straight up, this forest is
very dangerous.
Going into this forest is like chopping off one's own foot.
Now I am telling you this
because ever since I have
seen the forest and looked at it very carefully,
a very crazy idea has come to my mind.  I have a
very naughty idea.
That is, why don't we go inside this dangerous forest
and see whether we will be
able to survive inside this forest
or not.  Let's go and see and first we have to
convince the sisters to go there.
So friends, I have come
to my sisters and let us ask them whether
they want to go or not?  So my
dear sisters,
do you also want to come with me?
Where?   Hey,
speak here.
So when grandfather sees mother then he is very happy.
Where do you want to go?  Hey, there is that forest behind us, so
we will go there
and stay there for the night.   No no no,
he will not go.
Why?   There
are many big animals there.
Where?   There are
wild boars with such big teeth.
Okay, what
else can I do to get rid of it?   She is
scaring me into telling a lie.   I am
not lying.  Don't go.  This is such a flower like
daughter of mine.  Don't take them.
Yes, no, take it.
This flower-like girl is a witch herself.  This
is a witch.
[Music]
So friends, it's absolutely true that at
night here we hear strange animal
screaming sounds.  But the real fun will
come only when there is something there.  That's why will it be
fun to stay there or not?
Forgive me.  I don't want to go.
Why?
No brother, I don't want to go.   Let's go, it will be
fun.
No brother, I beg you.   Don't take
me away.
Shikha.
Brother, I am folding my hands from a distance.
Next time you did a ghost vlog,
I was really scared.  I am not going.
Brother, please leave me.  I am not going.   I
told my dear sister, listen, your brother
Dheeraj is with you, so what is there to be afraid of? So,
I will not go to the ghost vlog also.
Why are you scared, I will save you. Don't worry,
okay, let me know whether she wants to go or
not. Now it's
okay, I trust you. I will trust you once again and
see, so let's go. So
friends, Shikha is ready to go,
now I ask Mango, if Mango
would like to go, tell me, has she
become a ghost now, why wo
n't she come?
I made a ghost vlog, when she got scared in it,
friends, Mango is also very scared of that ghost vlog
and she is also refusing to
go.  Leena, you come with me.
[sound of clearing throat]
Hey, it'll look good just the two of us going there alone.
She is leaving.
Yes, I
agreed.
I I Captain.  I am ready to go.
[Music]
She agreed.
I am not going.
So friends, finally Reena has also agreed to
go with us and stay there
and let us see whether we
can stay there or not.
Stay together.   I will
always be with you, don't worry till my death.
So my dear sisters are you excited?   Yes.
[screaming]
Ready?   Yes.   Yes.
So friends, all three of us are ready.  Our
bag is also ready.  Let's go then and
survive in the jungle.  Come.  So
friends, another guy is going with us and
that is Lallu the Don.
So my three soldiers are you ready?
Ready.
For jungle adventure?
Yes boss.   Is there anything to be
afraid of?
No.
Sure?
Sure.
Oh
so friends let's go, come now,
oh friends let's go and face the eight,
oh friends let's go,
Mummy ji, see, all three of us including me, all
four of us are ready to go, okay let's go,
brother will take good care of
my flower like daughters,
yes that's right
Mummy is like a flower, pay a
little attention to her,
Mummy is not like a flower, she is a witch, seeing her
all the animals there are going to run away.
So okay,
okay.   Come on, please
bless us, Mom, that we
return safely the way we are going.   Let's go
safely today.   Bye bye bye.
So friends, we have reached our Thar.
Friends, we have sat in our Thar.
Now it's just time to leave.
I am getting very excited.   Are
you the one who fears the most?  No, it wo
n't happen this time for sure, you will see, this time I will
show you that I am the son of a lion, hey
lion
body
friends, we are going to the jungle and
this is going to be the first experience of our life, I don't know
how it will be and it is rainy
weather, you see, it has rained a
little and if it
rains there, we will get completely drenched, it will be the first
experience of our life,
but [laughs] it will be the first
experience,
first experience,
first
experience,
oh Reena knows English, yes
Jeena knows English.
Well friends, let's leave the talk and move on.
Move your car.  This is how you
start your car.  This is the start of our
power break.
Look friends, this is the forest behind our house.
Friends, the jungle has started.
Dense and very scary.
Oh my God.
What do I need?  So friends, see, we have
come to the forest and now it is our turn from here.   Let's take them.
What?   Let's take them along.
They are with us.  His blessings will always be
with us.  So now it's time
[music] to go down into the woods and
find a place where we
can set up camp and stay.  [MUSIC] There's
no need to be afraid.  I am with you.
Ok?
What?   There is
no need for any of you three to be afraid.
I am with you and this is my
rifle.  Okay, right?  [laughter] I'm
not even getting up.
This girl will run away first.  Look how
dense the forest is.
So friends, it seems safe here and we will
park our car here and
go on foot from here because there is no way for a car ahead.
So we will have to leave the car here and go.
Open it carefully and look underneath to make sure there is
no snake.
Brother, why are you scaring me?
Not right now, come on.   Lets go.   Even
if he sees you, you will be a snake.  Then he
will say my sister has come.  My sister has come.
Let's go friends.  Pick up your bag, brother.   Is it too
heavy?
Correct.   Should
I take it?
No, I will take it.   Come on, there is
no need to put it.  Now what to
put?
Mod.   Come on.
Friends, let's stop our car here.
They install the gate.  I am leaving it here.
Because this is the way.  If
unfortunately some problem arises or something goes
wrong, we will immediately run away
from there, get into our car, and if there is a
road nearby, we will immediately leave for home.
So, are you three ready to enter the jungle
?
Ready sir.
Now look, we are going to enter this forest
from here and will go inside from here.   Shall we
go?   Let us go.
Come let's go.
Where is it?
Friends, now we have entered the forest
and we are looking for our camping
place.
Where can we set up camping?
This is yours only.  So friends, look here, have
we just invented it?
Look here, Shika's house has been found.  Go and hide
in your hole.
Look, let's go to that side.
Oh brother, one more bone,
mummy,
what friends, look here, how many bones are there,
look here, here,
oh friends, look at this bone, it looks like
I am going home, I had
told you, I had told you that there are
such animals here who
eat the entrails of dead humans and animals, that is,
they eat their flesh, those people, go away, go away slowly,
look carefully, there are thorns ahead,
look ahead, see what you are doing, look carefully, you cannot
walk, come, do
not make any noise to anyone, if there is any
animal here, it will come hearing our voice.
Whoever wants to come, come, I am watching everyone.   You don't
call like this, you don't invite anyone.
Come on,
comment invited
friends, look there is a mound there.
Go over there and see what the forest is like. [Music]  Come
friends, see how many snake
holes there are here.  Look how many there are.  And
look, all these are of python or king cobra or
maybe black snake.  Hey, there is no
problem, come and give me your hand, don't fall,
give me your hand and
look
this way
friends, we have crossed such a dense forest and have reached a
high place.  How
was your experience brother?   There
is a heartbeat.
So let's set up camp here?
Lallu, I swear this is a very nice place.
Friends, it is good here but if it rains
from above then we will get drenched in the rain water.  That's why
we are not
staying here.  Let's look for a nice place.  There
is a river nearby, right?   Let's go to the
river bank and see
what happens there.  Come relax not by running
not by running can be animals.
If you go ahead and some animal comes and
catches you and Shika, you will run ahead
and some animal comes
and catches you, then how will we save
you?  Now go ahead.   I don't want to go
now.
Why?
Now whoever has more power will go.
Lallu
shut up.  Look there, what happened there?   There
he was,
hear the sound brother, the sound of wolves is coming,
these dogs are crying, it is not even night yet, let's go from
here, let's go to some other place, come, come, come, come,
friend, hey, from here, from here, not from here, where did you come from,
look, come, come, come, come here, come quickly, come quickly,
friends, the sound of very loud screaming of animals was
coming from above and these sisters of mine, who were
calling themselves brave, got
very scared for a second and said, don't stop here.
Brother, I have forgotten where to go.   From
here or from here straight straight
straight friend where did we come from?  Which way did you
come from?
Friends, look at this dense forest from the side, we have got lost in this forest.   Hey, don't be
afraid.  He is your brother.   Do you want to
go from this side or this side
?   Will
work.  [sound of clearing throat] Let's
go this way, this way.
Friends, we are going to
look for a place for camping somewhere else because there was a
very loud sound of animals crying there.
So we will look for some other good place.
Go from this side.   Let's go straight ahead.
Yes, come on, come on.
What in front?
That dog comes again and again.  [laughter]
Come on, come on.  Don't be afraid.  Come on.  The dog came
forward.   Let us go.   Come come.
Friends, we are going to a nice place.
Where we can
find a good place for camping.
And we will go to the river bank because there is
a little field on the river bank, so
we will set up camp there itself.  Look
carefully
friends, finally after wandering in the forest for 30 to 40 minutes,
we found another bone.
Friends, I will now show you how big the
animal's bone is.
[Sound of throat clearing]
Shakti,
forget that, I am going to tell you that from
here in front, here here in front,
look, from here we can see the river straight ahead.
So we are going near the river
because there will be open ground there, so we will set up the
tent there.  We will do our camping
there.  Ok?  Shall we go?   Let us go.   Let us go.
Friends, look, this is the bone that I just
told you about.  I don't know which animal it belongs to.
Look how beautiful this eye is.
Yes.
I think some meat
eating animal must have eaten its eye.  And just like that he will take
out your eyes and eat them.
[laughter] You'll see.   Without any issue.   What else
?  So
ignoring this bone, we go to the
river bank where we have to camp.  Shall we
go?   Let us go.   Yes.   Come on.
So friends, we are about to reach our destination.  There
is a river in front.   I am feeling
scared.
What are you afraid of?
You know I saw it on the podcast.
What did you see?  I have heard it too.
What?
Like you and I have brought some things for cooking.   There was
one boy in it, that is, we were a group.  Like
we have our whole group.  That group had
gone out for some trip or
camping, so they had prepared food and drinks.
So the ghosts come after smelling the fragrance.
Hey, why are you so scared?
You created a blog there for the first time.
Hey sisters, there is nothing to be afraid of.
We are all together.  And no ghosts etc. are
coming here.  Ok?  And friends,
look, we have reached the river bank.  This is the
place where the river is.  This is the Yamuna river of Agra.
We are going to see this river once.   Let's
go and see.  Now take it easy.
Easy.  Look how
fast they are doing it.  Are you mad?  Look, this
is a river.  Right on the river bank, this water is so
cold and what is this Shikh doing here
?  What are you doing?   I
am a river, brother.   If it had
fallen now.  [laughter] If you had
fallen right now, go away.  So friends, now let's go
up and
see a place for camping.  Come on, now we have to see
where we can set up camp here.   Why don't you
hurry up and take your time?  Yes, that is true.
Seeing, seeing [laughs] Seeing, seeing, seeing,
what not, do you have a
hobby of committing suicide?
It was about to fall down this slope.
His foot slipped here.
What were you going to do now?
Well friends, don't pay attention to his actions.
She is a bit naughty type.  And if it had
fallen now, all the work would have been spoiled.  Right here.
Friends, we are going on this telly.  We will
set up our camp here.  come soon.  Come come.  Come on board.   Please take it.
Come come look up carefully, there is
no life left in the body, come give me your hand
[sound made through the nose]
so friends we have decided at this place
that we will set up our camp here, yes it is a
good place, isn't it, yes we are getting a
very nice view, is it true, so
see this will be
our view of the river in front and our camp will be set up here, so come
how will it look, it will look
good, if you like it then
set up the camp
or come let's go, let's
clean it here?
Yes, let's clean it up a bit.  So, we
came here with shovels.  See.  He had brought a shovel.
So let's start.  If the place is
good then you will like our camp, right?
And we will also be able to stop properly.
Okay friends.  It has become clear here.
Now let's open our backpack and
take out the camping bag.  Open the bag.
And this is our camping bag.  Here is
our bag.  Now let's quickly open it and
set up our tent.  The sun has set
but before that we will set up camp so that
we can enter our camp before nightfall
and we do not face any problem.
Well, this is the first time we are doing all this, so
I am getting very excited.
Seriously,
hold this much down.   It worked.
Yes.
This is it.  Take out the other stick.  picking.
This is ours.
I am feeling good.  He is very
excited about this.
This is our tent being set up.  Look
friends, it worked.   I
picked this up from here and applied it to him.  No, no, not there.  It
felt like this in it.
Friends, look, our tent is ready.
How are you feeling?
We have to go inside it.  Later, first we will
put a rain cover on it because look at the weather, it is
so rainy, hence we will have to
put a rain cover also.  Pick it up
friends, this is our cover so that if it rains from above, it does
not wet us.
Friends, look, the sun has completely set and it
is about to be night and the sound of clouds is coming from there.  It
seems like it is about to rain
but
our tent is already set up before it rains.  Friends, look, this is
our tent.  We will
go inside it like this and sit here.  Hey come out, hey
no brother, I have not
gone yet.
No,
look, it has started raining a little.  Look,
small drops are falling.  But
we have set up our tent.  So we will be saved from the rain.
I am putting on the light.   Are you
putting up the lights?  Where?  Did
you guys bring these lights?
I have brought it.
Put it on then?
I am very excited.
This is the mat that we brought to
spread here.  take catch catch let me take.
This became our mat.  We will
sit here and enjoy it.  We will
sit here.  This is our view of the river from right in
front and we will have great camping here.
See what she is doing?   Are
you
feeling hungry?  Then make it.  Start making Maggi.
Take out that stuff, that.
What can I get?
Labour friends, this is our camp,
friends, our camp is
eating Maggi Pakora.
Eating Maggi.   Come
quickly, we will be late.   Come fast.
Friends, this is all our stuff.  Friends,
look, there are some light drops of
rain falling. Now, before the rain becomes too heavy, let
us make Maggi because we are
very hungry and there is no need for us to be scared of the rain
because we have a tent, so let us quickly
make Maggi and eat it. Then we go
inside the tent. We have to fit our gas cylinder in it
like this. Friends, we have fitted this gas
cylinder and our stove is ready. The
entire stove for Maggi is
ready, we keep it here.
We have enough cold water to make Maggi and it is
raining here slowly, there is no
need for light, I am
scared, it is
raining,
our gas has burnt, see
how dark it has become?
Put it.  Add water to it to make Maggi.
Friends, please make Maggi.  Now we will eat Maggi
and have fun brother.
Give me Maggi.  Throw away the Maggi.  This is
my Maggi.  Come closer.  Look, he is putting
his Maggi.  Its Maggi.
So friends, we have added Maggi and it is
raining.  Lightly.  I am
adding Maggi masala.  Maggi will be prepared simultaneously in this.  Are.
Yes.
We are making it quickly.
Then we will sit inside and eat.   We will
sit inside and eat because we cannot burn it inside, friend.  The
tent might catch fire.
We will eat it raw.
Friends, Maggi is being made in such rain.
Brother, it became a next level experience.
We did not think that it would rain so heavily
here.
Friends, how is it feeling to have such fun in the jungle,
my dear sisters?   Are you
not feeling scared?  And I forgot to tell you one thing.   Let me
tell you.   There is a
cremation ground at a short distance from here.   I am
telling the truth.  There is a cremation ground at a short distance.  Are you
not feeling scared?  If something
comes, there is no problem and look, it becomes
completely dark.  It's night now.
Brother,
I told you that the footcast
road was a little far from here.  Why are you scared
?
You also make it quickly, I don't
know.
Brother, take this
friends, it has become so dark here and the
sound of animals screaming has started coming.
Brother, I am really feeling a little scared.
I am feeling very scared.  Who was it?   It's
mom.
Made in color.  I think it has become.  Turn it off.  Turn it off.
Friends, look, our Maggi
is ready.  Look, here is our Maggi.
Now let's close it.  We have
turned off our gas.  So friends,
our Maggi is ready.  Now we will take Maggi inside
because it is raining here.
We have got a little wet.  We will sit inside and
eat.  Come on, let's keep it.  Come here.  Come here.
Guys [sound of clearing throat] it's
raining outside a little bit.
We got very wet.  She did
not come out.  She is surviving because of the cap.
Apply it.  So friends, our Maggi is
ready.  Now we will eat Maggi in this only.
Let's eat?
Look friends, look at our Maggi,
this glutton man did
not give it to me, the spoonful of
Maggi is ready.  He stood there holding a spoon.   I have
not given him the spoon,
take the spoon, give him the spoon.
Where from?
This greedy girl has not done any hard work
and yet she is the first one to eat.
Friends, can you hear the sound of rain
?  What kind of sound is this, pat pat pat pat pat
pat.
What?
I am eating.   He did not do
any work.  And look how she is fighting.   It
is very hot but brother, you do
n't eat food like that.   It
is very hot.  It is very tasty brother.  Will
Maggi really be so tasty?  Is Maggi tasty
or is it tasting good because of the hard work
we have put in?  What do you think
?   The
suffering makes the meat taste better.  So this
is the commentary.   There
is a vaccine.
Call me a spoon too.  I like everything.
Yes.  Whatever is available from haram,
no filter [laughs] unfiltered Reena, no
problem, I mean I just
said something on Badal's face today brother,
now look at Badal [laughs]
Badal, look how fast it is glowing, friends,
you see these people licked the whole Maggi, they gave
me just a little and this glutton is busy
drinking soup [laughs] she is
not giving it to me, do
n't fight friends, see our Maggi is over, it's your
turn, just lie down here comfortably
?   Is there
anyone near it?
Where?   Are you
mad?
Really?
Brother, stop, stop.
What is this?  So friends, we were eating Maggi
and suddenly we heard the sound of someone walking here.
Where is it visible?  That gas is
ours to see.  Where to look?  Look friends, look, look, look, he is
happy.  Look
away.
I am a dog.   There
is a different pleasure in sleeping after eating Maggi, brother.   I am having so much
fun.   I am
truthful.  I am feeling like the one we used to
see on TV in Man vs Wild, it is
raining like this while making Maggi,
Mummy, Bhaiya, I heard someone's voice just now, it was
some animal's voice,
Bhaiya, it must have been someone's, I don't know, let's go
out and see,
Bhaiya, no Bhaiya, don't be afraid, don't die, only a
voice is coming,
Lallu and I will go and see,
yes, there is no
dangerous animal here, we are going
alone, we
will also go back,
yes, I am sure you will
not be afraid, she is sleeping, don't be afraid at all.
No.   Will
you come?
Yes.   Come on.   Let us go.   It is
raining lightly outside.
No problem.  Don't leave.
Hey, why are you afraid?  Look friends, it became
dark here the whole night.
And friends, there is a cremation ground on the other side of it.   The
sound was coming from here.  Friends, all three of us are
outside the tent.  And look, it's
raining here.  And I am really feeling a little
scared.  Why?
Because some sound was coming from behind,
I thought let's go and see.  Come on, come on, let's
stay together.  Ok?   Wo
n't go in too much.
Not many will come in.  I will come and see.
Look friends, a strange sound of screaming was coming from somewhere in this place.
Hold my hand gently.  Are you together?
Slowly,
slowly.
Hey, come here.  Come this way.  Come this way.
Where was the sound coming from?
From this side.
Friends, the sound was coming from somewhere at this place.
Brother, don't go far,
friends, look
brother, let it be,
who is she going there,
brother,
look, look, look, friends, look at that place,
something like a shadow is visible, something strange,
friends, look, something like a shadow is visible, let's
not go, hey, we are going, haven't we come a
little, let's go,
hey, let's go to the
tent, we will go to the
tent, but if at night, yes, hey,
some sound came, at night, some animal
came near its tent.  Then what will we do?   Let's go and see.  I will come and see.
If there are
animals here then we will run away from
here.  Ok?
Let's see brother.  Ok.  Don't be afraid, there is no
problem.  Hey brother, your
friends are with you.  Why are
you scared?  What is this on the tree?
Brother, not us.
Brother, please come.
Mummy.
No brother, it is getting late.
Brother, please come.  Please brother.
Brother, where is this voice coming from just now?
Stay calm and relaxed.  Ok.
Look guys, get back here
guys.
Who is it?   There was a
strange sound coming from somewhere.  walk back walk back walk comfortably walk
comfortably walk don't.   Don't
shout, don't walk.  The animals will follow.  Do
n't shout.
Hey, why are you crying here and there?   leave
me behind.
Hey, what happened?
O dear.
Friends, here we can hear the
screaming sounds of very strange animals.  We wo
n't be able to stay here at night, friend.
People will be able to stop.
Brother,
she is very scared.   I will wait for now.
Friends, this is our tent.  We pack up our tents
and hurry out of here.   Get your
stuff out quickly.
Take out the tent stuff.  Hurry up, hurry up.   Stay
home.  Quickly.
Hurry up, hurry up, that's it.
I am really very scared.
My hands and legs are trembling.  I don't know
which animal it was brother.  We made a big mistake by
coming here.
Inside
brother, hurry up brother, hurry up brother.
So friend, I think we made a mistake by
coming here.  We should not go anywhere else.   Just now
some animal came.  Friends, let's go quickly.  Come on.   Let us go.
Friends, let us end the camping here.
We have packed the bags.  Come.
Friends, our experience is really very
scary.  And the animal sounds that are coming
from here,
what animals are they driving?
First I sit in the car and then I talk to you.
Ok.  I'll leave quickly.   I hope none of
my belongings are left.   Is there
any stuff left?
Hey, don't run ahead.   Come along.
Now I will
die.
Oye Oye where are you going?
We will die.
Where have you come and where are you coming?  Silent.  Shut up.
Left behind.
Where?
Hey, straight straight straight.  Hey, where are you running
?  Walk straight.  We came near our car.
Come quickly, come quickly, come quickly, come
quickly,
friends, finally we have reached the car
safely,
sit, sit, sit, sit,
hey, what happened, why are you worried, don't you want to
talk, not at home, come on
Tina, why are you so worried,
brother, we will
talk at home, let's go home, let's go home,
really friends,
I did not know what the
experience of camping is like, that too near the forest, we
go home and tell how it felt to us.
So friends, we have returned safely from the jungle
and now we are going to tell
you how our experience was there.
Lallu got a call from mom's house
so he had to go urgently, otherwise if he had
reached here then he would have told us how we felt staying there.  That was the
most
scary thing.   Was it
horror?
I am still in the same shock.  When we ran away.  I was
so scared.  I have come to Bagh-Bagh.
He is not there, he looked like a shadow which I found on the tree.  I thought
that someone might be sitting there,
yes
no, there was a tree there,
we were just lying in the tent,
suddenly we heard the sound of some strange animal and we did
not know which animal it was, so we went out
and started looking
which animal it was because we were
not supposed to go there at night, if we do
not go and look first then who knows it might come to
us at night, how will we be able to see it suddenly, so we
went out and looked, there was a tree there
and some strange white shadow was sitting on the tree,
yes
really,
and we also saw the eyes of that animal.   I
swear, from a distance, as we were climbing up, as soon as we
went up the tree, the animal suddenly looked at us and
looked towards the tree, then
yes
you saw it, now see it in the video,
see it in the blog, I
swear, so
friends, this was our experience which
we told you, it was really very
scary because the sounds of the animals were
scaring us a lot, so
now we will stay like this very rarely at night, we will
watch only during the day, at night we
held our ears, so now you tell me how you liked this blog, if you liked it then
like it, subscribe to the channel
and tell in the comment
which was your favorite moment.  Ok?
See you in the next vlog.